{
    "id": "e59593d7fc9f4ce78167f1970cb60681",
    "title": "Gerund Or Infinitive",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have …………………. soon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to go",
                "going"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cf6495ed4aa94a88b399cada6a4fc41b"
        },
        {
            "question": "They refused …………………… the matter any further.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to discuss",
                "discussing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c71e9e0ebb6c4265b38bdb88f813fbd0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He threatened ………………… me if I didn’t give him the key.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to shoot",
                "shooting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8d7c6f0ae89442648dca5006c51fb52c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I promise …………………… you tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "visiting",
                "to visit"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a8a98981cd4c4699a129e283c8b16442"
        },
        {
            "question": "He intends …………………… a business.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to start",
                "starting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "54e836a2e09d466db5dee70f9622b8bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher taught the children …………………  the truth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to tell",
                "telling"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4baf983e8fb043d2a7b47ed5f5bfb82f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Jack told me …………………… dressed in ten minutes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to get",
                "getting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "da18f85ca0e74b7b84660ef1bff4c444"
        },
        {
            "question": "Susie wishes ………………… music.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to learn",
                "learning"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "952a367c405d442192258427237a6073"
        },
        {
            "question": "He learned ………………….. English in six months.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to speak",
                "speaking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2f968ed591bc4d1ba0c083e91ac438b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I dared him ……………………  across the river.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "jumping",
                "to jump"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fe0c3ecfa17241cab2de9a2d559b84de"
        }
    ]
}